question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Seoul is the capital of North Korea.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                                   "question": "The Cold War ended with Joseph Stalin&#039;s death.",
                                                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the play Oedipus Rex, Oedipus kills his father due to jealousy in loving his mother.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The animated film &quot;Spirited Away&quot; won the Academy Award for Best Animated Feature at the 75th Academy Awards in 2003.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The Xenomorph from the science fiction film &quot;Alien&quot; has acidic blood.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Theodore Roosevelt Jr. was the only General involved in the initial assault on D-Day.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "&quot;The Division Bell&quot; is the final album of the progressive rock band Pink Floyd.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In association football, or soccer, a corner kick is when the game restarts after someone scores a goal.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are commonly referred to as &quot;Black Elves&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                   "question": "Franz Joseph I was the last emperor of Austria.",
                                                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
